It's really inside.
すごい中で入ってるよ
Amazing inside.
すごい中
dangerous.
危ない
I'll put it in.
入れちゃうよ
Open with sound.
音で開いて
Open it.
開いて
dangerous.
危ない
So can I just go?
じゃあ行っちゃっていいの?
I'll go.
行くよ
Where can I take it out?
どこ出していい?
I'll bring you something.
何か出しちゃうよ
I'll go.
行くよ
It probably came out a lot.
めっちゃ出た、多分
About 2 liters came out.
2リットルくらい出た
No, seriously, seriously.
いや、マジマジマジ
I can't go if I put in that much.
そんくらい入れたら行けない
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Please stop that angle.
その角度止めててね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
good?
いい?
difficult.
難しい
I think I'm going to go.
行っちゃいそうな
So can I just go?
じゃあ行っちゃっていいの?
I'll go.
行くよ
Where can I take it out?
どこ出していい?
I'll bring you something.
何か出しちゃうよ
I'll go.
行くよ
It turned out great, I guess.
すげー出た、多分
It probably came out a lot.
めっちゃ出た、多分
About 2 liters came out.
2リットルくらい出たな
No, seriously, seriously.
いや、マジマジマジ
I can't go if it comes out like that.
そんくらい出たら行けない
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I'll put this in at the same time as Nick.
ニックと同時にこれ入れるからね
my player
俺の選手
I'm really into it.
めっちゃ入れてるわ
This is terrible.
やばい、これ
perhaps.
多分
It's the highest record ever.
過去最高記録出たのね
The highest record ever.
過去最高記録の
My shoulder feels like it's going to fall off.
肩が外れそう
This is definitely coming out really well.
めっちゃ出てるよ、これ絶対
This is crazy.
これやば
This is terrible.
やばい、これ
Awesome.
すげー
It's coming out great, would you like to see it?
すげー出てるよ、見る?
I'll show you later.
後で見せてあげる
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Don't move now.
今動かないでね
This really came out.
やっぱこれめっちゃ出たわ
He's really quiet.
なんかめっちゃ黙ってるもん
Well done, this is it.
できたね、これね
Did you do this too?
これもできた?
this.
これ
It's reaching your uterus.
届いてるもんだって、子宮に
It penetrated my uterus.
貫通したよ、子宮
I want to show you how amazing it is.
すげー見せてあげたい
A lot of white sperm is coming out.
すっげー白い精子いっぱい出てる
Out of focus.
ピントが合わない
Ah, I can see it.
あ、見えてきた
It's completely different, after all, from the beginning.
全然違うわ、やっぱ最初と
It's different from the first time.
最初とは違う
The really white one is stuck.
すごい白いのが止まってる
Wow, this is really thick semen.
やばい、これめっちゃ濃厚な精子
This is thick semen.
濃厚な精子だよ、これ
It's foamy.
泡状になってるわ
It's too amazing.
凄すぎて
It moved, it moved.
動いた動いた
It's moving, it's moving.
動いてる動いてる
It moves so much when I laugh.
すげー動いてる笑うと
It's really, really moving.
めっちゃ、めっちゃ動いてる
It's moving amazingly.
すげー動いてる
I'm dancing.
ダンスしてる
The sperm was dancing.
精子がダンスしてた
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Well then, let's pull it out.
じゃあ、抜くね
If you pull it out, it'll probably come out as a mess.
抜いたらね、多分ドロって出てくる
I'll pull it out.
抜くよ
It hurts.
痛いよ
picture?
え?
Did it hurt?
痛かったの?
My breath feels weird.
僕の息がなんか変な感じする
It's so bad, my sperm is already overflowing.
なんかやばい、精子もう溢れてる
Ah, ah.
あー、あー
The wind system came out.
風気系出てきた
Spread it out.
広げて
Ah, this is done.
あー、これ出来たな
It was done.
出来ちゃった
Her pussy is wide open.
おまんこパックリ開いてるよ
I can see the hole from here in your pussy.
おまんここっから穴見えるんだけどな
Awesome.
すげー
Now, let's finish by cleaning the tip.
じゃあ最後、先っぽを掃除して終わろう
It's early.
先っぽね
Same tip as before.
前と同じ先っぽで
It's getting really white.
めっちゃ白くなってる
What does it smell like?
どんな匂いする?
sour.
酸っぱい
What's the smell?
匂いは?
The smell of pussy.
お まんこの匂い
The smell of semen.
精子の匂い
lie?
うそ?
Really?
本当に?
What does semen smell like?
精子どんな匂いするの?
Does it smell like my semen?
俺の精子臭いかな?
It smells like fish.
魚臭い
thank you.
ありがとう
Okay, did you lick it?
よし、舐めた?
now.
今
You licked it.
舐 めたじゃん
Really?
本当に?
I licked it.
舐めたじゃん
Finally, please give us your thoughts.
じゃあ最後、ちょっと感想お願いします
Same as before though.
前と同じだけどね
how was it?
どうだった?
Today, I was actually planning on cosplaying, but...
今日ね、本当はね、コスプレするつもりだったんだけど、
You're wearing a uniform, you're cosplaying.
制服のね、コスプレしちゃったんだよね
how was it?
どうだった?
So next cosplay.
じゃあ次コスプレ
Are you going to do cosplay next?
次コスプレやる?
Yeah.
うん
uniform?
制服?
uniform.
制服
Is the uniform okay?
制服はいい?
Don't you want to do something else?
他なんかやりたいのないの?
Hey, you're making onions, aren't you?
ちょっとさ、まんねぎしてるでしょ、
Because.
だって
Don't you want to do something a little different?
ちょっと 変わったことやりたくない?
What has changed?
何変わったこと?
Well, I'll do a little something on the train.
じゃあなんかさ、電車の中でさ、ちょっとやっちゃったりする
how?
どうやって?
Is it impossible?
無理か
Is that impossible?
それ無理か
So you want to do something different.
じゃあなんか変わったことやりたいんだよね
It's something I've never seen before.
なんか、今までにないやつ
So, can I collect some requests?
じゃあちょっとリクエスト集めてきていい?
yes.
はい
Well then, please give me one last thing.
じゃあ最後になんかください
Look at this work.
この 作品を見て
thank you.
ありがとうございます
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
Well then, let's cosplay this time.
じゃあ今度はコスプレでね
Good night then.
じゃあおやすみなさい
bye bye.
バイバイ